http://www.harlequinbeads.com/privacy-policy-p2

Seed Beads
Czech CharlotteCzech MiniDuoCzech PonyCzech SeedCzech SuperDuoCzechMate BarCzechMate BrickCzechMate TriangleMiyuki cubeMiyuki delicaMiyuki seedMiyuki tila
Swarovski
Swarovski Crystal BeadsSwarovski Pearl BeadsSwarovski PendantsSwarovski Closeouts
Metal
ButtonsChainCharmsCoinsFindingsMetal BeadsMetal Wire
Glass Beads
Czech Bead MixesCzech Pressed GlassCzech Handmade Lampwork
Specialty Beads
Ancient Roman GlassHandmade GlassCzech Glass ButtonsMirage beads
Natural Beads
Bone BeadsClay BeadsClay BottlesGemstone Beads
Stringing Materials
Beading NeedlesFirelineGriffin NylonGriffin SilkHemp TwineIrish Waxed LinenK.O. threadLeather CordNymo ThreadRat Tail Satin CordSoft Flex WireStretch MagicStringth bead cordSuperlon bead cordTigertail (cable)
Jewelry Kits
BraceletsEarringsNecklaces
Tools
Clearance
Gallery
Jewelry Design Ideas
Shared Designs
Swarovski Designs
Privacy Policy
At Harlequin Beads & Jewelry, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect to assist us in processing orders. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.The Information We Collect: Harlequin Beads & Jewelry collects from you the necessary information, such as name, email address, address and payment information, to process orders.We Do Not Share Your Personal Information: Harlequin Beads & Jewelry does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. This information is for our private records only. We restrict access to your orders to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. Personal information is not available to any third party via our website or through other means.Spam Email and Use of Email Addresses: We make every effort to minimize the amount of email correspondence you receive from us. We do not share or sell your email address to any third parties.Use of Cookies: Harlequin Beads and Jewelry uses cookies to enhance your shopping and browsing experience and keep track of your order information. The cookies we use DO NOT store any personal information such as your e-mail address, street address or phone number.Do you still have questions? If you have additional questions or wish to further discuss details of our privacy policy, please feel free to Contact Us.
